EXPERIMENTS TO DISSEMINATE
BLUEPRINTS FOR PLAGUES."
WOULD YOU LIKE TO ANSWER ONE
QUESTION AND LET US KNOW WHETHER
OR NOT YOU HAVE CHANGED YOUR
MIND ON WHETHER OR NOT THE
BENEFITS OF GAIN OF FUNCTION
RESEARCH OUTWEIGH THE RISKS?
DR. FAUCI: ON THE ADVICE OF
COUNSEL, I RESPECTFULLY DECLINE
TO ANSWER BASED
UPON MY RIGHTS UNDER THE FIFTH
AMENDMENT TO THE CONSTITUTION.
CHAIR PAUL: THE CHAIRMAN HAS
DENIED YOUR ASSERTION OF
PRIVILEGE AND DIRECTED YOU TO
ANSWER BUT YOU NONETHELESS
REFUSE AND STAND ON PRIVILEGE
DESPITE THE EXISTENCE OF A
PARDON.
THE COMMITTEE WILL HAVE TO
CONSIDER AFTER THIS HEARING MORE
APPROPRIATE ACTION SHOULD BE
TAKEN AGAINST YOU FOR THE
FAILURE TO TESTIFY AFTER BEING
DIRECTED TO DO SO.
IT IS AGAINST THE LAW TO
OBSTRUCT AN INVESTIGATION OF
CONGRESS.
THERE WILL BE REPERCUSSIONS TO
REFUSAL TO TESTIFY TODAY.
SENATOR PETERS?
YOU ARE NOT RECOGNIZED.
IF YOU'RE UNRULY YOU WILL BE
REMOVED FROM THE PROCEEDING.
YOU ARE NOT RECOGNIZED.
SIR, YOU ARE NOT RECOGNIZED.
SECURITY?
WE WILL HOLD OFF.
YOU WILL RESPECT THESE
PROCEEDINGS.
YOU WERE TOLD NOT TO SIT AT THE
TABLE, YOU INSIST ON SITTING AT
THE TABLE WE TOLD YOU YOU WOULD
NOT BE RECOGNIZED.
YOU ARE NOT INVITED HERE FOR
TESTIMONY, SIR.
YOU ARE BEING DISRUPTIVE.
WOULD YOU BEHAVE THIS WAY IN A
COURTROOM?
THE JUDGE WOULD PUT YOU IN JAIL.
I CANNOT DO THAT TODAY BUT I
WOULD HAVE YOU ESCORTED FROM THE
PREMISES.
I WOULD SAY SIT QUIETLY AND DO
NOT SAY ANOTHER WORD.
YOU ARE NOT RECOGNIZED.
ANOTHER WORD AND YOU ARE GONE.
SEN. PETERS: I WOULD LIKE TO
HEAR WITH THE ATTORNEY HAS TO
SAY.
CHAIR PAUL: HE IS NOT RECOGNIZED
BY THE COMMITTEE OR THE CHAIR.
IF HE SPEAKS AGAIN HE WILL BE
REMOVED FROM THE ROOM.
THIS TESTIMONY IS FROM ANTHONY
FAUCI.
THIS IS NOT A GAME FROM HIS
LAWYERS.
HIS LAWYERS CAN GIVE HIM ADVICE.
THEY ARE ALL ALLOWED TO TALK TO
HIM.
THE ATTORNEYS ARE NOT
RECOGNIZED.
THE ATTORNEY WAS TOLD NOT TO SIT
AT THE TABLE AND HE IS NOT A
BANG THAT RECOMMENDATION.
THERE IS A ROW BEHIND YOU WHERE
YOU WERE TOLD TO SET.
NOW YOU ARE DISRUPTING THE
PROCEEDINGS.
THIS IS THE WAY ANTHONY FAUCI
WANTS TO BE REMEMBERED, FOR A
LAWYER NOT LISTENING TO THE
RULES.
YOU ARE NOT RECOGNIZED.
CHAIR PAUL: SECURITY, PLEASE
REMOVE HIM FROM THE ROOM.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
CHAIR PAUL: LET THE RECORDS
STATE THAT DR. FAUCI WILL STILL
HAVE THE ADVICE OF THE OTHER
HALF-DOZEN ATTORNEYS HE BROUGHT
ALONG TODAY.
SENATOR PETERS.
SEN. PETERS: THANK YOU.